Mss.Ms.Coll.109
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence, 25.25 linear feet
  - Roheim, Ge'ra, 1939; 3 items (Box 42)
  - Rolfe, Randy Colton, 1988; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Romney, Seymour L, 1958; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ronder, Paul, 1969; 1971; 2 items (Box 42)
  - Rook, A.J, 1953; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Roosevelt, Edith Kermit, 1958; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1953; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rose, F.G.G, 1963; undated; 2 items (Box 42)
  - Rose, Jack A, 1971; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rose, Larry, 1981; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rose, Steven, 1979-1996; 18 items (Box 42)
  - Rosenberg, Debbie L, 1982; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rosenberg, Hans, 1957; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rosenblum, Louis, 1947; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rosenfeld, Louis, 1948; 1949; 7 items (Box 42)
  - Rosenfield, Richard E, 1972; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rosenthal, Arthur J, 1977; 1982; 2 items (Box 42)
  - Rosenthall, Gertrude, 1969; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rosenwald, Ruth Frank, 1982; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rosenzweig, Saul, 1964; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rosling, Norman W, 1962; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rosnick, Yvonne, 1978-1985; 36 items (Box 42)
  - Ross, B. Robert, 1972; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ross, Barbara, 1989; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ross, Jean W, 1981; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ross, Norman P, 1962; 2 items (Box 42)
  - Rosten, Leo, 1968; undated; 2 items (Box 42)
  - Roszak, Theodore, 1994; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Roth, Sanford H, 1953; 2 items (Box 42)
  - Rotteveel, Jacqueline, 1981; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Roueche, Berton, 1963; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rousseau, George, 1964-1967; 3 items (Box 42)
  - Rowan, William, 1934-1942; 17 items (Box 42)
  - Rowe, Sarah L, 1977; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Royle, Nicholas, 1987; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rubik, Beverly, 1995; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rubin, Joan Shelley, 1995; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rubin, Jerry, 1978; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ruch, T.C, 1941; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rudan, Paveo, 1971; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ruckberg, Leah, 1994; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ruesch, Jeffrey, 1976; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ruesch, Jurgen, 1958; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ruggiero, Vincent Ryan, 1992; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rule, Colter, 1964-1965; 3 items (Box 42)
  - Rumney, Jay and Rebecca, 1955; October 20; April 23; 3 items (Box 42)
  - Rushbrook, Margaret, 1972; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Rusk, Michal Herridge, 1981; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Russ, Kenneth, 1970; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Russell, Bertrand, 1936-1952; 3 items (Box 42)
  - Russell, Sally, undated; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Russell, W.L, 1959; 4 items (Box 42)
  - Russianoff, Penelope, 1978; 1989; 2 items (Box 42)
  - Rutledge, Lyman V, 1977; 1 item (Box 42)
  - Ryley, Andy, undated; 1 item (Box 42)
  - R-Misc, 1946-1993; 17 items (Box 42)
  - Sabin, Albert, 1957; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sable, Ruth, 1972; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sachs, Albie, 1974; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sachs, Benjamin D, 1966; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sachs, Connie, 1981; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sackler, Arthur M, 1956; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sackler, Mortimer D. MD, 1955; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sackler, Tani, 1980; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sagan, Eli, 1985; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Sagarin, Edward, 1962; 1966; 3 items (Box 43)
  - St. John, Ian, 1982; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sait, Mrs. Bernard, 1951; 1964; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Sahlins, Marshall, 1965; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Salamone, Frank A, 1985; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Salk, Jonas, 1980; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Salvador, Jane, 1981; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Salvermini, Gaetano, 1944; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Salzman, Leon MD, 1972; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Samuel, Maurice, 1956; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Samuels, Curtis, 1978; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Samuels, Gertrude, 1977; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sandbeck, Michael, 1971; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sanders, Chauncey, 1953; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sanders, Marc, 1989-1997; undated; 7 items (Box 43)
  - Sanders, Stephanie, 1995; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sanford, Carl N, 1970; 3 items (Box 43)
  - Sanford, R. Nevitt, 1945; 1962; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Sangorski and Sutcliffe, 1959-1960; 16 items (Box 43)
  - Sargent, E.N, 1968-1969; 3 items (Box 43)
  - Sargent, Porter, 1947-1965; 58 items (Box 43)
  - Sargent, Stan and Ginny, 1955; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Sarton, George and May, 1934-1997; 26 items (Box 43)
  - Sataloff, Joseph MD, 1963; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Saul, Leon J. MD, 1979; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Saunders, G.B.deC.M, 1943; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Savory, Teo, 1961-1973; undated; 8 items (Box 43)
  - Saxton, Mark, 1971; 4 items (Box 43)
  - Sayre, Anne, 1969; 1972; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Scaer, Roberta, 1994; undated; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Scaglione, A, 1964; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Scarr, Sandra Wood, 1978; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Schact, C, 1966; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schacter, Harry, 1968; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schacter, Sara, 1967; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Schada, Steven, 1987; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Scheffer, Victor B, 1985; 1989; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Scheinfeld, Amram, 1951-1973; undated; 9 items (Box 43)
  - Scheinfeld, Dorothy, 1979; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schein, Herman, 1964; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schene, Paul, 1983; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schiavo, Donna, 1975; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schielke, Carl, 1983; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schiff, L.I, 1946; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schilling, David, 1976; undated; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Schlipp, Paul A, 1965; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schirmer, William, 1945; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schmidt, Charmion, 1987-1990; undated; 8 items (Box 43)
  - Schmookler, Andrew Bard, 1989; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schneider, Ginny, 1979; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schneider, Scott, 1977; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schneirla, T.C, 1942; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schoen, Claire, 1978; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schoenbaum, S, 1971; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schoenstein, Ralph, 1985; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schommer, Terry, 1984; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schroeder, Patricia, 1987; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schulman, Grace, 1974-1992; 4 items (Box 43)
  - Schulman, Jack, 1971; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schultz, Adolph H, 1930-1946; 10 items (Box 43)
  - Schultze, Burt, 1964; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schuman, Bill, 1946; 1950; 4 items (Box 43)
  - Schuman, Henry, 1948; 1950; 3 items (Box 43)
  - Schuster, M. Lincoln, 1936; 1957; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Schwartz, Harold MD, 1963; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schwartz, Leni, 1981; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schwartz, Leonard, 1982; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schwatrz, Paula, 1984; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Schwartz, Penny, undated; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schweig, David A, 1975; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, 1952; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Schweitzer, Gertrude, 1955; 1967; 3 items (Box 43)
  - Sciortino, R, 1953; 1 item (Box 43)
  - SCM Corporation, 1966; 1967; 3 items (Box 43)
  - Scott, D.H, 1961; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Scott, J.P, 1973; 1974; 2 items (Box 43)
  - Scribner, Charles III, 1980; 1 item (Box 43)
  - Seadler, Stephen Edward, 1995; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Searchinger, Gene, 1978; 3 items (Box 44)
  - Seaton, Ethel, 1936; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sebeock, Thomas A, 1980; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Seeds, Peggy, 1980; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Seeger, Pete, 1983; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Seeley, Theresa, 1971; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Segal, Jonathan, 1981; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Seidenscwartz, Kristin, 1989; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Seitz, Mrs. George, 1966; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Selden, Steven, 1985-1998; undated; 24 items (Box 44)
  - Seldes, George, 1941-1986; 5 items (Box 44)
  - Seligman, C, 1938; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Seligmann, Herbert J, 1939; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Selsam, Howard, 1942; 1943; 3 items (Box 44)
  - Selunt, Herman, 1957; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Selye, Hans, 1975; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Semans, Sarah, 1990; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Semple, Mrs. Bruce, 1976; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sempliner, Edna, 1941; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sengstack, Arlene, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Serlin, Ilene, 1990; undated; 3 items (Box 44)
  - Sewak, John H, 1992; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Seymour, Lillian, 1972; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sgarlato, Thomas E, 1971; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shafer, Barbara, April 12; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shaffer, Joseph, 1977; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shah, Saleem A, 1969; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shallit, Joseph, 1942; 1983; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Shaltz, Joseph, 1940; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shanks, Elisabeth MD, 1982; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shanley, Laura Kaplan, 1993; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shapiro, Evelyn (Mrs. Karl), 1965; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shapiro, H.A, 1939; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shapiro, Harry, 1937; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shapiro, H.L, 1941; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shapiro, Selma, 1965; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sharer, Wesley E, 1970; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Sharp, David, 1985; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sharp, Eliot H, 1984; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sharp, R. Lauriston, 1936-1941; 4 items (Box 44)
  - Shatzer, Barbara, 1972; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shaw, C.J.H.M, 1972; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shea, Susan C, 1995; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sheedy, Charlotte, 1982; 1983; undated; 26 items (Box 44)
  - Sheehan, Thomas, 1980; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sheldon, William H, 1943; 1942; 4 items (Box 44)
  - Shelley, Carole, 1979; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Sherman, Editta, 1958; 1990; 3 items (Box 44)
  - Sherman, Susan, 1992; 1993; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Sherry, Earl C, 1981; 3 items (Box 44)
  - Sherwin, Raymond J, 1965; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sherwin, Oscar, 1945; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shields, Andrea, 1977; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shiff, Sidney, 1990; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shiloh, Ailon, 1958; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shippen, Elizabeth, 1955; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shire, Betty, 1981; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shirtliff, Diana, 1966; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shlain, Leonard M. MD, 1991; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Shlain, Nina, 1930; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shoneff, Tom and Julie, 1981; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shore, Bradd, 1983; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Shorr, Ephraim MD, 1941; 1949; 3 items (Box 44)
  - Short, Steven, 1983; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shostrom, Everett L, 1982; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shrader, James H, 1956; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shultz, Gladys Denny, 1955; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Shumaker, David, 1972; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Siegel, Bernard S. MD, 1993; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sigerist, Henry E, 1939-1947; 5 items (Box 44)
  - Sigmund, Barbara B, 1990; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Sills, David L, 1964; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Silver, James W, 1965; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Silverman, Jacob, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Silverman, Rachel E, 1996; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Silverman, Simon, undated; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Silverton, Nevil, 1956; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Silvette, Herbert, 1938-1962; 12 items (Box 44)
  - Simmonds, Louis, 1940; 1985; 6 items (Box 44)
  - Simmons, Larry O, 1984; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Simmons, Roy T, 1947; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Simons, Paule Yves, 1966; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Simons, Calvin H, 1989; 1 item (Box 44)
  - Simons, Elwyn, 1963-1967; 4 items (Box 44)
  - Simpson, Eileen, 1978; 1979; 3 items (Box 44)
  - Simpson, George E, 1965; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Simpson, George Gaylord, 1959; 1981; 2 items (Box 44)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1958; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Singer, June, 1983; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Singer, Charles, 1936-1954; 12 items (Box 45)
  - Singer, Ronald, 1955-1964; 4 items (Box 45)
  - Singerman, Joseph, 1939; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Sinnott, E.W, 1953; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Skenes, Robert E, 1979; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Skerlj, Bozo, 1952-1961; 6 items (Box 45)
  - Skewes-Cox, B, 1969; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Skinner, B.F, 1982; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Skinner, Cornelia Otis, 1952; undated; 3 items (Box 45)
  - Skjeie, Linden, 1988; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Skloot, Ed, 1969; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Skrube, Frank, 1997; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Slaughter, John, 1981; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Sloan, Dorothy, 1987; 1988; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Sloane, Joseph C, 1968; 1969; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Sloane, William, 1972; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smallwood, Joan, 1975; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, A.T, 1956; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, Barbara, 1986; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, Cathy, 1981; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, Charles E, 1968-1983; 3 items (Box 45)
  - Smith, Clement A. MD, 1963; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, Colin, 1984; 1988; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Smith, DeWitt, 1955; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, John Maynard, 1978; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, Karen D.L, 1981; 3 items (Box 45)
  - Smith, Kendra, 1979; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, L.F, 1952; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, Marian W, 1952; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, Mary Carol, 1977; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Smith, Nan, 1978; 3 items (Box 45)
  - Smith, Page, 1965-1981; 8 items (Box 45)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1984; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smith, Scott S, April 5; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Smyth, Nathan A, 1936; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Snodgrass, Jeral W, 1981; 1982; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Snow, C.P, 1962; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Snow, Charles E, 1947-1960; 8 items (Box 45)
  - Snyder, Laurence H, 1950; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Snyder, Louis L, 1945; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Sobel, Jeff, 1986; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Sobell, Laura, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Solecki, Ralph S, 1959-1964; 3 items (Box 45)
  - Soli, Girorgio, 1989; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Solomon, Barbara, 1991; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Somers, Wayne, 1972; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Somerson, Paul, 1978; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Sooy, Howard C, 1972-1977; 3 items (Box 45)
  - Sorokin, Pitirim A, 1942-1956; 42 items (Box 45)
  - Sourin, Peter, 1967; 1975; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Sourian, Zareh, undated; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Spadoni, Carl, 1981; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Spaeth, Edmund B, 1942-1974; 14 items (Box 45)
  - Spaeth, George L, 1966-1989; 13 items (Box 45)
  - Spaeth, Lee, 1967; undated; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Spaeth, Merrie M, 1966; undated; 6 items (Box 45)
  - Spaeth, Philip G, 1976-1977; 5 items (Box 45)
  - Sparks, Ashley Montagu, 1989-1995; 4 items (Box 45)
  - Spaulding, Preston T, 1989; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Spears, Lillian, 1963; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Speck, F.G, 1943; 1 item (Box 45)
  - Spector, Novera Herbert, 1988-1994; undated; 19 items (Box 45)
  - Speech, 1963; 1966; 6 items (Box 45)
  - Spencer, T, 1943; undated; 2 items (Box 45)
  - Spiro, Melford E, 1968-1975; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Sprio, Robert H, 1971; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Spitz, Rene A, 1941-1963; 13 items (Box 46)
  - Spitzer, Robert S, 1988; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Spock, Benjamin, 1974-1968; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Sprague, Samuel C, 1984; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Squier, Robert J, 1966; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Stace, Walter and Blanche, 1957-1979; 14 items (Box 46)
  - Staley, Larry A, 1982; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stalnaker, Luther W, 1943; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stanciu, George, 1990; 1991; 4 items (Box 46)
  - Stanfield, John H. II, 1991; 1994; 4 items (Box 46)
  - Stanley, Steven B, 1977; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stanton, Frederick L, 1931; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Starne, Roberta, 1981; undated; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Stavrianos, L.S, 1984; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Steedman, E, 1949; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Steadman, Frances, 1958; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Steeghs, Peter, 1990; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Steele, Myra, 1982; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1942-1946; undated; 13 items (Box 46)
  - Steffen, Linda, 1982; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Steggerda, Morris, 1950; undated; 4 items (Box 46)
  - Steigerwald, Mary, 1982-1984; undated; 12 items (Box 46)
  - Stein, Howard F, 1980; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Steinberg, Isador, 1959; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Steinem, Gloria, 1968; 1970; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Steiner, George, 1968; 1971; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Steiner, Stan, undated; 4 items (Box 46)
  - Stendler, Celia B, 1962; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stephens, Ralph R, 1997; 1998; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Stern, Bernhard J, 1940-1945; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Stern, Frederick M, 1975; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stern, J. David, 1952-1964; 11 items (Box 46)
  - Sternberg, Maurice, undated; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stetsear, Ulli, 1991; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stevens, Melissa Harris, 1983; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stevenson, Lois, 1970; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stevenson, Mary Lou, 1982; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stevenson, Paul Huston, 1938; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Stewart, David, 1984; 1988; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Stewart, Debra, 1981; 1982; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Stewart, Robert Sussman, 1972; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stewart, T. Dale, 1941-1959; 4 items (Box 46)
  - Stillerman, Elaine, 1992; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stocking, George W. Jr, 1986; 1987; 12 items (Box 46)
  - Stoddard, George D, 1971; 1982; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Stoër, Micheline, undated; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stone, A. Harris, 1996; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stone, Florence, 1984; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stone, M.K, 1967; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Stone, Marshall E, 1980; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stone, Rick, undated; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Storrs, Arnold B, 1971; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stradner, Mary C, 1980; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Strandskov, Herluf H, 1945; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Straus, Donald B, 1974; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Straus, William L. Jr, 1957-1963; 4 items (Box 46)
  - Strehlow, Kathie, 1977-1979; 1981; 12 items (Box 46)
  - Streissguth, Ann Putkowicz, 1978; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Strieber, Edward M, undated; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stroke, 1994; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Strong, W. Duncan, 1937; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Strongin, Herb, 1977; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Strothman, Wendy J, 1990; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stroup, Timothy, 1978-1984; 10 items (Box 46)
  - Strunsky, Robert, 1967; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Stuart-Macadam, Patty, 1995; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Stulman, Julius, 1967; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Sturtevant, William C, 1965; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Sugarman, Muriel MD, 1977; 1978; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Suk, V, 1937; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Sullivan, Harry Stack, 1938; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Sullivan, Margaret, 1982; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Summer, Anita, 1977; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Sundermeyer, Niels, 1966; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Super, R.H, 1955; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Susskind, David, 1967; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Sussman, Ronnie, 1990; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Sutherland, Malcolm R, undated; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Sutton, Harvey, 1941; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Swack, Janice, 1981; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Swanson, Gloria, 1967; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Swanton, John R, 1953; 1957; 6 items (Box 46)
  - Swarth, Oscar S, 1968; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Swing, Raymond, 1946; 3 items (Box 46)
  - Swinton, W.E, 1981;1982; 2 items (Box 46)
  - Symmons, K, 1956; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Syz, Hans, 1954; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Szamek, Pierre, 1982; 1 item (Box 46)
  - Szent-Gyorgyi, Albert, 1980; 1 item (Box 46)
  - S-Misc, 1942-1995; 43 items (Box 46)
  - Sheets-Johnstone, Maxine, 1 of 4, 1985-1988; 13 items (Box 47)
  - Sheets-Johnstone, Maxine, 2 of 4, 1989; 31 items (Box 47)
  - Sheets-Johnstone, Maxine, 3 of 4, 1990-1995; 14 items (Box 47)
  - Sheets-Johnstone, Maxine, 4 of 4, 1989; 1990; undated; 11 items (Box 47)
  - Talbott, John H, 1962-1966; 4 items (Box 48)
  - Taliaferro, Marlene, 1977; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tanaka, Sumiko, 1955; undated; 3 items (Box 48)
  - Tanner, Nancy M, 1988; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tapp, Robert B, 1995; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Targ, William, 1957-1990; undated; 18 items (Box 48)
  - Tarsius, 1939-1947; undated; 10 items (Box 48)
  - Tart, Charley, 1994; 1995; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Tax, Sol, 1946-1976; undated; 5 items (Box 48)
  - Taylor, Clayton Jon, 1976; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Taylor, Frank E, 1982; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Taylor, G. Dekle MD, 1971; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Taylor, Gordon Rattray, 1958-1983; undated; 18 items (Box 48)
  - Taylor, Laurence J, 1990; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Taylor, Robert C, 1977; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Taylor, Robert E, 1983; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Taylor, Sybil, 1991; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Taylor, Theodore, 1976-1993; 7 items (Box 48)
  - Taylor, William S, 1971; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tead, Ordway, 1956-1965; 3 items (Box 48)
  - Teele, Rev. Roger, 1983; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tekiner, Roselle, 1993; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Temple, Paul, 1988; 1990; undated; 3 items (Box 48)
  - Tengelsen, Walter E, 1982; undated; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Tennant, James R, 1982; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Terrace, H.S, 1975; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Terry, R.J, 1937; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Terzian, Sherry, 1968; undated; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Tessler, Sandy, 1977; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Theodorakopoulos, Manos I, 1996; 4 items (Box 48)
  - Therra, Henry, 1969; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thevenin, Tine, 1989; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thibault, Suzanne, 1977; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thoma, Andor, 1966; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thomas, Alexander, 1961; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thomas, Cal, 1981; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thomas, Charles C, 1943; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Thomas, Hoben, 1981; 1989; 3 items (Box 48)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1963; 1967; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Thompson, Barbara E, undated; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thompson, Carole, 1981; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thompson, Frank Jr, 1968; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thompson, Helen, 1938; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thompson, Kenneth W, 1956; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thompson, Laura, 1954; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thompson, Pat, 1982; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thompson, Stith, 1941; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thompson, William R, 1954; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Thorndike, Lynn, 1943; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Thornton, John F, 1970; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Throop, Cheri, 1987; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Tietze, Christopher, 1960; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tiger, Lionel, 1970-1982; 9 items (Box 48)
  - Tildesley, M.L, 1937-1938; 4 items (Box 48)
  - Time Magazine, 1942; 1967; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Tivenan, Bonnie, 1982; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tjio, J.H, 1959; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tobach, Ethel, 1971-1980; 3 items (Box 48)
  - Tobias, Michael, 1981; 1982; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Tobias, Phillip V, 1959-1994; 27 items (Box 48)
  - Todd, Jack, 1980; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Todd, T. Wingate, 1931-1954; 10 items (Box 48)
  - Tokay, Elbert, 1967; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tolliver, Peter, 1970; 1977; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Tomkins, Sylvan, undated; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tompson, Marian, 1964; 1994; undated; 3 items (Box 48)
  - Townsend, Claire, 1981-1984; 6 items (Box 48)
  - Toynbee, Arnold, 1955; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Travis, Joan and Arnold, 1980; 1981; 3 items (Box 48)
  - Treloar, Alan E, 1983; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Trembley, Fran, 1971; 3 items (Box 48)
  - Trevor, J.C, 1936; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tricules, Homer, 1950; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Truby, Henry, 1984; 1989; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Tunin, Mel, 1967; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Turck, Charles J, 1958; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Turko, Michael, 1970; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Turnbull, Colin, 1975-1988; 5 items (Box 48)
  - Turner, Ralph E, 1952; 5 items (Box 48)
  - Turney-High, Harry, 1964; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tuttle, Helen, 1975-1982; undated; 4 items (Box 48)
  - Tuttle, Preston, 1981; 2 items (Box 48)
  - Tuzin, Donald, 1990; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tydings, J. Mansir, 1969; 1 item (Box 48)
  - Tyson, 1936-1980; 22 items (Box 48)
  - T-Misc, 1962-1983; undated; 4 items (Box 48)
  - Ubell, Robert, 1977; 1980; 2 items (Box 49)
  - Ulmer, Frederick A., Jr, 1948; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Underwood, E. Ashworth, 1946-1954; 12 items (Box 49)
  - Underwood, Lee, 1967; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Underwood, W.A, 1977; 1 item (Box 49)
  - United Airlines, 1989; 1992; 2 items (Box 49)
  - United Nations Committee of ISRA, 1985; 1 item (Box 49)
  - United States Bureau of Indian Affairs, undated; 1 item (Box 49)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, undated; 1 item (Box 49)
  - United States Information Agency, 1963; 1 item (Box 49)
  - University of Pennsylvania Press, 1984; 3 items (Box 49)
  - Unruh, Jess, 1970; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Unsworth, Richard P, 1972; 3 items (Box 49)
  - Ure, Mary, 1973; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Urschel, Betsy, 1981; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Urschel, Harold C, 1982-1990; undated; 6 items (Box 49)
  - Vaasamoorti, 1980; 1981; 2 items (Box 49)
  - Vahanian, Paul, 1969; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Valenstein, Elliot S, 1975; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Valentine, Charles, 1972; 1974; 8 items (Box 49)
  - Vallejo, Alfonso, undated; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Vallois, H.V., 1946-1963; 9 items (Box 49)
  - Van Camerick, Stephen B, 1977; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Van Doren, Irita, 1952; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Van Doren, Ruth, 1980; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Van Doren, William, 1978; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Van Fleet, Bradley, 1984-1991; undated; 13 items (Box 49)
  - Van Gelder, Robert, 1945; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Van Riet Lowe, 1950; 1951; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Vasconcellos, John, 1975; 1977; undated; 5 items (Box 49)
  - Vaughn, William, 1995; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Veillon, James B, 1990; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Velton, H.V, 1934-1936; 19 items (Box 49)
  - Venables, Peter H, 1971; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Ventura, Michael, 1991; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Verlag, Gustav Fischer, 1959; 1 item (Box 49)
  - Verner, Susan, 1995; 1 item (Box 49)